

## About me

I'm a Frontend Web Developer with one year of experience. I'm pretty good at HTML and CSS. Now, I'm learning JavaScript and have already made two projects with it.. Besides web stuff, I've been doing Graphic Design and Video Editing for four years, using lots of different software

### **Contact**

- **Q** 0313-5291256
- talhacodingproject.github.io/Talha-malik
- Main Bazar Saidpur Islamabad

## **Expertise**

- Graphic Designing
- Video Editing
- Frontend Development
- Data Entry

## Talha Malik

Frontend Developer

#### **Education**

2019 - 2024 Haris shaheed Model School Main Bazar, Saidpur Village, Islamabad, Pakistan

#### Certification

2023 - 2024 Viral University (Wordpress) Meta facebook (MS Specialist)

# **Work Experience**

2021 - 2024

- Work on different graphic designing apps.
- Design logos, banners and brochures for different projects.
- Edit videos like a pro level editor using Capcut, Canva, and Clipchamp.

#### 2023-2024

- Work passionately on HTML, CSS and JS.
- Develop 9 website using HTM, and CSS.
- Create a portfolio project using bootstrap.